# Shuo-Jen, Chang

#### DIGITAL CONSULTANT

■ andrew90524@gmail.com | • Anguschang582 | • shuojen-chang

#### **Summary** \_

Currently an Analyst at Accenture Japan Ltd, I specialize in maintaining and refining Android application, ensuring its stability and seamless functionality for a substantial user base. My expertise encompasses feature enhancement, bug resolution, and systematic testing, with a focus on delivering consistent app improvements.

As a data science enthusiast, I hold the title of Kaggle Competition Master and I always love participating in data science-related competitions in my free time. This affords me the chance to learn from top talent and address a diverse set of challenges posed by businesses and institutions. Through these experiences, I've honed my skills in applying AI solutions across industries and extracting valuable insights from vast datasets in a wide range of scenarios.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Accenture Japan Ltd**

Tokvo, Japan

ANALYST

Nov. 2022 - Present

- Manage and maintain Android application with over millions of users, This includes promptly addressing and mitigating application-related incidents and bugs,
  as well as executing quarterly updates in alignment with client requests.
- Conducted large-scale testing for quarterly updates, ensuring the robustness and reliability of the application ahead of each release. Designing new test cases to meticulously evaluate newly added functionalities or resolved bugs.

Taiwan (R.O.C) Army

Miaoli, Taiwan & Taichung, Taiwan

Dec. 2021 - Mar. 2022

PRIVATE (COMPULSORY MILITARY SERVICE)

- · Successfully completed intensive training sessions, acquiring comprehensive instruction in shooting techniques, firearm maintenance and bayonet drills.
- Garnered small team management experience on a combat readiness mission, coordinating and leading a team to ensure optimal preparedness and performance.

#### **Honors & Awards**

#### INTERNATIONAL

2022	21st Place / 4875 teams	American Express Default Prediction	American Express, Google(Kaggle)
2018	21st Place / 1094 teams	PLAsTiCC Astronomical Classification	LSST Project, Google(Kaggle)
2018	2nd Place / 7198 teams	Home Credit Default Risk	Home Credit Group, Google(Kaggle)
2018	7th place / 1917 teams	Avito Demand Prediction Challenge	Avito, Google(Kaggle)

#### DOMESTIC

2020	1st Place & MVP	P&G Japan IT Tech Challenge 2020	P&G Japan
2020	1st Place / 110 teams	Re: Real Estate Transaction Price Prediction	Probspace
2019	1st place	DeNA Data Science Competition for Students #1	DeNA Co., Ltd.
2019	7th Place / 366 teams	MyNavi x SIGNATE Student Cup 2019	Signate

#### Skill

**Back-end** Django, Spring Boot **Programming** R, Python, JAVA, Kotlin, ੴR

**Languages** Chinese(Native), English(Native), Japanese(Intermediate)

#### **Education** \_\_\_

## Tokyo Institute of Technology (東京工業大学)

Tokyo, Japan

M.S IN MATHEMATICAL AND COMPUTING SCIENCE

Sep. 2019 - Sep. 2021

**Soochow University** 

Taipei, Taiwan

B.A. IN ECONOMICS

Sep. 2015 - Jun. 2019

## Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Kaggle Competition Master**

KAGGLE Since 2018.

- · Currently hold 2 gold medals, 5 silver medals and have consistently ranked in the top 3% in various Kaggle competitions.
- Have joined over 15+ competitions, topics included the unsolved problems in astrophysics, biology field, default prediction for banks, insurance claim prediction, and visitor/value/stock price/demand prediction.